<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 2/22/2015 3:58:52 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FA-18">
		<Text>Boeing F/A-18C Hornet - Strike Fighter</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_FA-18">
		<Text>American Air Unit designed to perform air to ground attacks or strike missions on an aircraft carrier or land based aviation platform.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FA-18_STRATEGY">
		<Text>The American F/A-18C Hornet is a powerful air unit. It can be based in any city you own or aboard an aircraft carrier. It can move from base to base and can perform strike missions within its range of 9. It's primary role is as a strike aircraft or bomber, so it provides that function, but from a sea or land based location, which sets it apart from the Stealth Bomber unit, unlocked with later technologies.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_FA-18_TEXT">
		<Text>The McDonnell Douglas (now Boeing) F/A-18 Hornet is a twin-engine supersonic, all-weather carrier-capable multirole combat jet, designed as both a fighter and attack aircraft (F/A designation for Fighter/Attack).[NEWLINE]Designed by McDonnell Douglas and Northrop, the F/A-18 was derived from the latter's YF-17 in the 1970s for use by the United States Navy and Marine Corps. The Hornet is also used by the air forces of several other nations. The U.S. Navy's Flight Demonstration Squadron, the Blue Angels, has used the Hornet since 1986.[NEWLINE]The F/A-18 has a top speed of Mach 1.8 (1,190 mph or 1,915 km/h at 40,000 ft or 12,190 m). It can carry a wide variety of bombs and missiles, including air-to-air and air-to-ground, supplemented by the 20 mm M61 Vulcan cannon.[NEWLINE]It is powered by two General Electric F404 turbofan engines, which give the aircraft a high thrust-to-weight ratio. The F/A-18 has excellent aerodynamic characteristics, primarily attributed to its leading edge extensions (LEX).[NEWLINE]The fighter's primary missions are fighter escort, fleet air defense, Suppression of Enemy Air Defenses (SEAD), air interdiction, close air support and aerial reconnaissance. Its versatility and reliability have proven it to be a valuable carrier asset, though it has been criticized for its lack of range and payload compared to its earlier contemporaries, such as the Grumman F-14 Tomcat in the fighter and strike fighter role, and the Grumman A-6 Intruder and LTV A-7 Corsair II in the attack role.[NEWLINE]The Hornet saw its first combat action in 1986 during the 1986 United States bombing of Libya and subsequently participated in 1991 Gulf War and 2003 Iraq War.[NEWLINE]The F/A-18 Hornet provided the baseline design for the Boeing F/A-18E/F Super Hornet, a larger, evolutionary redesign of the F/A-18.[NEWLINE]Information Credit - WikiPedia</Text>
	</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YF23">
			<Text>Northrop YF-23 Black Widow II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_YF23">
			<Text>Air Unit designed to perform air to ground attacks or strike missions as an aircraft carrier or land based aviation platform.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YF23_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The YF-23 Black Widow II is a powerful advanced stealth air unit. It can be based in any city you own or aboard an aircraft carrier. It can move from base to base and can perform strike missions within its range of 25. It's primary role is as a strike aircraft or bomber, so it provides that function, but from a sea or land based location, which sets it apart from the Stealth Bomber unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_YF23_TEXT">
			<Text>The Northrop/McDonnell Douglas YF-23 was an American single-seat, twinjet Stealth fighter aircraft technology demonstrator designed for the United States Air Force (USAF). The design was a finalist in the USAF's Advanced Tactical Fighter (ATF) competition, battling the Lockheed YF-22 for a production contract. Two YF-23 prototypes were built with the nicknames "Black Widow II" and "Gray Ghost".[NEWLINE]In the 1980s, the USAF began looking for a replacement for its fighter aircraft, especially to counter the USSR's advanced Sukhoi Su-27 and Mikoyan MiG-29. Several companies submitted design proposals; the USAF selected proposals from Northrop and Lockheed. Northrop teamed with McDonnell Douglas to develop the YF-23, while Lockheed, Boeing and General Dynamics developed the YF-22.[NEWLINE]The YF-23 was stealthier and faster, but less agile than its competitor. After a four-year development and evaluation process, the YF-22 was announced the winner in 1991 and entered production as the Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor. The U.S. Navy considered using the production version of the ATF as the basis for a replacement to the F-14, but these plans were later canceled. The two YF-23 prototypes were museum exhibits as of 2009[NEWLINE]-Credit Wikipedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HARRIER">
			<Text>AV-8B Harrier II - Jump Jet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_HARRIER">
			<Text>Stong Air Unit designed to perform air to ground attacks or strike missions as an aircraft carrier or land based aviation platform.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HARRIER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The American, Italian, Spanish and English AB-8B Harrier II - Jump Jet, is a powerful air unit. It can be based in any city you own or aboard an aircraft carrier. It can move from base to base and can perform strike missions within its range of 11. It's primary role is as a strike aircraft or bomber, so it provides that function, but from a sea or land based location, which sets it apart from the Stealth Bomber unit, unlocked with later technologies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_HARRIER_TEXT">
			<Text>The McDonnell Douglas (now Boeing) AV-8B Harrier II is a single-engine ground-attack aircraft that constitutes the second generation of the Harrier Jump Jet family. Capable of vertical or short takeoff and landing (V/STOL), the aircraft was designed in the late 1970s as an Anglo-American development of the British Hawker Siddeley Harrier, the first operational V/STOL aircraft. Named after a bird of prey, it is primarily employed on light attack or multi-role missions, ranging from close air support of ground troops to armed reconnaissance. The AV-8B is used by the United States Marine Corps (USMC), the Spanish Navy, and the Italian Navy. A variant of the AV-8B, the British Aerospace Harrier II, was developed for the British military, while another, the TAV-8B, is a dedicated two-seat trainer.[NEWLINE]The project that eventually led to the AV-8B's creation started in the early 1970s as a cooperative effort between the United States and United Kingdom (UK), aimed at addressing the operational inadequacies of the first-generation Harrier. Early efforts centered on a powerful revamped Rolls-Royce Pegasus engine to dramatically improve the capabilities of the Harrier. Due to budgetary constraints, the United Kingdom abandoned the project in 1975.[NEWLINE]Following the withdrawal of the UK, McDonnell Douglas extensively redesigned the earlier AV-8A Harrier to create the AV-8B. While retaining the general layout of its predecessor, the aircraft incorporates a new wing, an elevated cockpit, a redesigned fuselage, one extra hardpoint per wing, and other structural and aerodynamic refinements. The aircraft is powered by an upgraded version of the Pegasus, which gives the aircraft its V/STOL ability. The AV-8B made its maiden flight in November 1981 and entered service with the USMC in January 1985. Later upgrades added a night-attack capability and radar, resulting in the AV-8B(NA) and AV-8B Harrier II Plus, respectively. An enlarged version named Harrier III was also studied, but not pursued. The UK, through British Aerospace, re-joined the improved Harrier project as a partner in 1981, giving it a significant work-share in the project. After corporate mergers in the 1990s, Boeing and BAE Systems have jointly supported the program. Approximately 340 aircraft were produced in a 22-year production program that ended in 2003.[NEWLINE]Typically operated from small aircraft carriers, large amphibious assault ships and simple forward operating bases, AV-8Bs have participated in numerous military and humanitarian operations, proving themselves versatile assets. US Army General Norman Schwarzkopf named the USMC Harrier II as one of the seven most important weapons of the Gulf War. The aircraft took part in combat during the Iraq War beginning in 2003. The Harrier II has served in Operation Enduring Freedom in Afghanistan since 2001, and was used in Operation Odyssey Dawn in Libya in 2011. Italian and Spanish Harrier IIs have taken part in overseas conflicts in conjunction with NATO coalitions. During its service history, the AV-8B has had a high accident rate, related to the percentage of time spent in critical take-off and landing phases. USMC and Italian Navy AV-8Bs are to be replaced by the Lockheed Martin F-35B Lightning II, with the former expected to operate its Harriers until 2025.[NEWLINE]Information Credit - WikiPedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_F117">
			<Text>F-117 Nighthawk - Stealth Fighter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_F117">
			<Text>Advanced Stealth Air Unit designed to perform air to ground attacks or strike missions as a land based aviation platform.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_F117_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The American F-117 Nighthawk - Stealth Fighter, is a powerful air unit. It can be based in any city you own. It can move from base to base and can perform strike missions within its range of 15. It's primary role is as a strike aircraft or bomber, so it provides that function, but from a sea or land based location, which sets it apart from the Stealth Bomber unit, unlocked with later technologies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_F117_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Lockheed F-117 Nighthawk is a single-seat, twin-engine stealth ground-attack aircraft formerly operated by the United States Air Force (USAF) developed from the Have Blue technology demonstrator and produced by Lockheed's Skunk Works. It is the first operational aircraft to be designed around stealth technology. The maiden flight of the F-117 happened in 1981 and the aircraft achieved initial operating capability status in October 1983.[1] The Nighthawk spent much of its early service life shrouded in secrecy, until it was revealed to the world in November 1988.[NEWLINE]Information Credit - WikiPedia
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RAFALE">
			<Text>Dassault Rafale - Strike Fighter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_RAFALE">
			<Text>French, Egytpian and Indian Air Unit designed to perform air to ground attacks or strike missions as an aircraft carrier or land based aviation platform.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RAFALE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Dassault Rafale is a powerful air unit. It can be based in any city you own or aboard an aircraft carrier. It can move from base to base and can perform strike missions within its range of 12. It's primary role is as a strike aircraft or bomber, so it provides that function, but from a sea or land based location, which sets it apart from the Stealth Bomber unit, unlocked with later technologies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_RAFALE_TEXT">
			<Text>The Dassault Rafale is a French twin-engine, canard delta-wing, multirole fighter aircraft designed and built by Dassault Aviation. Equipped with a wide range of weapons, the Rafale is intended to perform air supremacy, interdiction, aerial reconnaissance, and nuclear strike missions.[NEWLINE]In the late 1970s, the French Air Force and Navy were seeking to replace and consolidate their current fleets of aircraft. In order to reduce development costs and boost prospective sales, France entered into an arrangement with four other European nations to produce an agile multi-purpose fighter. Subsequent disagreements over workshare and differing requirements led to France's pursuit of its own development program. Dassault built a technology demonstrator which first flew in July 1986 as part of an eight-year flight-test programme, paving the way for the go-ahead of the project. The Rafale is distinct from other European fighters of its era in that it is almost entirely built by one country, involving most of France's major defence contractors, such as Dassault, Thales and Safran.[NEWLINE]Many of the aircraft's avionics and features, such as direct voice input, the RBE2 AA active electronically scanned array radar and the Optronique secteur frontal infra-red search and track sensor, were domestically developed and produced for the Rafale programme. Originally scheduled to enter service in 1996, the Rafale suffered significant delays due to post-Cold War budget cuts and changes in priorities. The aircraft is available in three variants: Rafale C single-seat land-based version, Rafale B twin-seat land-based version, and Rafale M single-seat carrier-based version.[NEWLINE]Introduced in 2001, the Rafale is being produced for both the French Air Force and for carrier-based operations in the French Navy. While the Rafale has been marketed for export to several countries, it has only been selected for purchase by the Indian Air Force and the Egyptian Air Force. The Rafale has been used in combat over Afghanistan, Libya, Mali and Iraq. Several upgrades to the weapons and avionics of the Rafale are planned to be introduced by 2018.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_F-14">
			<Text>Grumman F-14 Tomcat - Inteceptor/Fighter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_F-14">
			<Text>American Air Unit designed to perform Air to Air combat missions with limited ground strike capability based from an aircraft carrier or from land.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_F-14_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grumman F-14 Tomcat is a powerful modern air unit, that excels in air to air combat.  It can be deployed aboard an aircraft carrier, or from a city/airfield.  It has extended range for a fighter/inteceptor with a range of 13, which gives it the capability to provide air escort for a naval battlegroup or extended enemy strike possibilities.  All Jet Fighters are especially effective against enemy helicopters. All Jet Fighters has the "air recon" ability, which means that everything within 6 tiles of its starting location is visible at the beginning of the turn. See the rules on Aircraft for more information.[NEWLINE]American pilot training is known as some of the best in the world, to reflect that, the F-14 will gain experience faster with successfull missions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_F-14_TEXT">
			<Text>The Grumman F-14 Tomcat is a fourth-generation, supersonic, twinjet, two-seat, variable-sweep wing fighter aircraft. The Tomcat was developed for the United States Navy's Naval Fighter Experimental (VFX) program following the collapse of the F-111B project. The F-14 was the first of the American teen-series fighters, which were designed incorporating the experience of air combat against MiG fighters during the Vietnam War.[NEWLINE]The F-14 first flew in December 1970 and made its first deployment in 1974 with the U.S. Navy aboard USS Enterprise (CVN-65), replacing the McDonnell Douglas F-4 Phantom II. The F-14 served as the U.S. Navy's primary maritime air superiority fighter, fleet defense interceptor and tactical aerial reconnaissance platform. In the 1990s, it added the Low Altitude Navigation and Targeting Infrared for Night (LANTIRN) pod system and began performing precision ground-attack missions.[NEWLINE]The Tomcat was retired from the U.S. Navy's active fleet on 22 September 2006, having been supplanted by the Boeing F/A-18E and F Super Hornets.  As of 2014, the F-14 was in service with only the Islamic Republic of Iran Air Force, having been exported to Iran in 1976, when the U.S. had amicable diplomatic relations with Iran.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_T50">
			<Text>Sukhoi PAK FA T-50 Stealth Fighter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_T50">
			<Text>Fighter Air Unit designed to perform Air to Air combat missions with limited ground strike capability based from an aircraft carrier or from land.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_T50_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grumman F-14 Tomcat is a powerful modern air unit, that excels in air to air combat.  It can be deployed aboard an aircraft carrier (grey Naval Version), or from a city/airfield (camo Air Base Version).  It has extended range for a fighter/inteceptor with a range of 13, which gives it the capability to provide air escort for a naval battlegroup or extended enemy strike possibilities.  All Jet Fighters are especially effective against enemy helicopters. All Jet Fighters has the "air recon" ability, which means that everything within 6 tiles of its starting location is visible at the beginning of the turn. See the rules on Aircraft for more information.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_T50_TEXT">
			<Text>The PAK FA (Perspektivny Aviatsionny Kompleks Frontovoy Aviatsii, literally "Prospective Airborne Complex of Frontline Aviation") is a fifth-generation fighter programme of the Russian Air Force. The T-50 is the aircraft designed by Sukhoi for the PAK FA programme. The aircraft is a stealthy, single-seat, twin-engine jet fighter, and will be the first operational aircraft in Russian service to use stealth technology. It is a multirole combat aircraft designed for the air superiority and ground attack functions. It combines supercruise, stealth, maneuverability, and advanced avionics to overcome previous generation fighter aircraft along with many ground and maritime defences.[NEWLINE]The PAK FA is intended to be the successor to the MiG-29 and Su-27 in the Russian Air Force and serve as the basis for the Fifth Generation Fighter Aircraft (FGFA) being co-developed by Sukhoi and Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) for the Indian Air Force.  The T-50 prototype first flew on 29 January 2010 and production aircraft is slated for delivery to the Russian Air Force starting in 2016. The prototypes and initial production batch will be delivered with a highly upgraded variant of the AL-31F used by the Su-27 family as interim engines while a new clean-sheet design powerplant is currently under development. The aircraft is expected to have a service life of up to 35 years[NEWLINE]Credit - Wikipedia
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MQ1">
			<Text>Predator MQ-1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_MQ1">
			<Text>Predator drone UAV, a modern recon and ranged unit</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MQ1_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The General Atomics Predator MQ-1 is a long range unmanned air unit used primarily for ground stike and surveillance missions.  This modern technology ensures if the aircraft gets shot down, the pilot who is at an undisclosed ground station will be safe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_MQ1_TEXT">
			<Text>The General Atomics MQ-1 Predator is an unmanned aerial vehicle UAV built by General Atomics and used primarily by the United States Air Force and Central Intelligence Agency. Initially conceived in the early 1990s for aerial reconnaissance and forward observation roles, the Predator carries cameras and other sensors but has been modified and upgraded to carry and fire two AGM-114 Hellfire missiles or other munitions.[NEWLINE]The aircraft, in use since 1995, has seen combat over Afghanistan, Pakistan, Bosnia, Serbia, Iraq, Yemen, Libya, Syria, and Somalia.[NEWLINE]The USAF describes the Predator as a "Tier II" MALE UAS - medium-altitude, long-endurance unmanned aircraft system. The UAS consists of four aircraft or air vehicles with sensors, a ground control station, and a primary satellite link communication suite. Powered by a Rotax engine and driven by a propeller, the air vehicle can fly up to 400 nmi - 460 mi; 740 km to a target, loiter overhead for 14 hours, then return to its base.[NEWLINE]Following 2001, the RQ-1 Predator became the primary unmanned aircraft used for offensive operations by the USAF and the CIA in Afghanistan and the Pakistani tribal areas; it has also been deployed elsewhere. Because offensive uses of the Predator are classified, U.S. military officials have reported an appreciation for the intelligence and reconnaissance-gathering abilities of UAVs but declined to publicly discuss their offensive use.[NEWLINE]Credit - Wikipedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SU25">
			<Text>Sukhoi SU-25 Frogfoot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_SU25">
			<Text>Sukhoi SU-25 Frogfoot fast attack Soviet made land based Bomber.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SU25_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sukhoi SU-25 Frogfoot is a long range bomber type air unit used primarily for ground stike and surveillance missions.  While this aircraft was initially developed in the 1960's, it remains deadly, with the plethora of upgrades by various nations, and is a true time tested warrior.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_SU25_TEXT">
			<Text>The Sukhoi Su-25 (NATO reporting name: "Frogfoot") is a single-seat, twin-engine jet aircraft developed in the Soviet Union by the Sukhoi Design Bureau. It was designed to provide close air support for the Soviet Ground Forces. The first prototype made its maiden flight on 22 February 1975. After testing, the aircraft went into series production in 1978 at Tbilisi in the Soviet Republic of Georgia. Russian air and ground forces nicknamed it "Gratch" ("Rook").[NEWLINE]Early variants included the Su-25UB two-seat trainer, the Su-25BM for target-towing, and the Su-25K for export customers. Some aircraft were being upgraded to Su-25SM standard in 2012. The Su-25T and the Su-25TM (also known as the Su-39) were further developments, not produced in significant numbers. The Su-25, and the Su-34, were the only armoured, fixed-wing aircraft in production in 2007.[1] Su-25s are in service with Russia, other CIS states, and export customers.[NEWLINE]The type has seen combat in several conflicts during its more than 30 years in service. It was heavily involved in the Soviet war in Afghanistan, flying counter-insurgency missions against the Mujahideen. The Iraqi Air Force employed Su-25s against Iran during the 1980–88 Iran–Iraq War. Most were later destroyed or flown to Iran in the 1991 Persian Gulf War. Abkhazian separatists used Su-25s during the Abkhazian War from 1992 to 1993. The Macedonian Air Force used Su-25s against Albanian insurgents in the 2001 Macedonia conflict and, in 2008, Georgia and Russia both used Su-25s in the Russo-Georgian War. African states, including the Ivory Coast, Chad, and Sudan have used the Su-25 in local insurgencies and civil wars.[NEWLINE]Credit - Wikipedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MIG15">
			<Text>MiG-15 Fagot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_MIG15">
			<Text>MiG-15 prop driven Soviet made land based Fighter/Intercepter.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MIG15_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The MiG-15 Fagot is a fast fighter type air unit used primarily for anti-air missions, it was used primarily by the communist nations in the World War II era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_MIG15_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mikoyan-Gurevich MiG-15 (NATO reporting name: "Fagot") is a jet fighter aircraft developed by Mikoyan-Gurevich OKB for the Soviet Union. The MiG-15 was one of the first successful swept-wing jet fighters, and achieved fame in the skies over Korea, where, early in the war, it outclassed all straight-winged enemy fighters in most applications.[NEWLINE]Later, the MiG-15 would also serve as a starting point for the development of the more advanced MiG-17. The MiG-15 is believed to have been one of the most widely produced jet aircraft ever made; in excess of 12,000 were manufactured. Licensed foreign production may have raised the production total to over 18,000.[1] The MiG-15 is often mentioned, along with the North American F-86 Sabre, as the best fighter aircraft of the Korean War, and among the best fighter aircraft of all time[NEWLINE]Credit - Wikipedia
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MIG29">
			<Text>MiG-29 Fulcrum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_MIG29">
			<Text>The MiG-29 Fulcrum is a fast attack Soviet made land based Fighter/Intercepter.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MIG29_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The MiG-29 Fulcrum is a fast attack land based fighter type air unit used primarily for anti-air missions, but has the capability as a multirole bomber/attacker.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_MIG29_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Mikoyan MiG-29 (NATO reporting name: "Fulcrum") is a jet fighter aircraft designed in the Soviet Union. Developed by the Mikoyan design bureau as an air superiority fighter during the 1970s, the MiG-29, along with the larger Sukhoi Su-27, was developed to counter new American fighters such as the McDonnell Douglas F-15 Eagle, and the General Dynamics F-16 Fighting Falcon. The MiG-29 entered service with the Soviet Air Force in 1983.[NEWLINE]While originally oriented towards combat against any enemy aircraft, many MiG-29s have been furnished as multirole fighters capable of performing a number of different operations, and are commonly outfitted to use a range of air-to-surface armaments and precision munitions. The MiG-29 has been manufactured in several major variants, including the multirole Mikoyan MiG-29M and the navalised Mikoyan MiG-29K; the most advanced member of the family to date is the Mikoyan MiG-35. Later models frequently feature improved engines, glass cockpits with HOTAS-compatible flight controls, modern radar and IRST sensors, considerably increased fuel capacity; some aircraft have also been equipped for aerial refuelling.[NEWLINE]Following the dissolution of the Soviet Union, the militaries of a number of former Soviet republics have continued to operate the MiG-29, the largest of which is the Russian Air Force. The Russian Air Force wanted to upgrade its existing fleet to the modernised MiG-29SMT configuration, but financial difficulties have limited deliveries. The MiG-29 has also been a popular export aircraft; more than 30 nations either operate or have operated the aircraft to date, India being one of the largest export operators of the type. As of 2013, the MiG-29 is in production by Mikoyan, a subsidiary of United Aircraft Corporation (UAC) since 2006.[NEWLINE]Credit - Wikipedia
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EUROFIGHTER33">
			<Text>Eurofighter Typhoon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_EUROFIGHTER33">
			<Text>Eurofighter Typhoon fast attack European land based Bomber.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EUROFIGHTER33_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Eurofighter Typhoon is a fast attack long range bomber type air unit used primarily for ground stike.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_EUROFIGHTER33_TEXT">
			<Text>The Eurofighter Typhoon is a twin-engine, canard-delta wing, multirole fighter. The Typhoon was designed and is manufactured by a consortium of three companies; Alenia Aermacchi, Airbus Group and BAE Systems, who conduct the majority of affairs dealing with the project through a joint holding company, Eurofighter Jagdflugzeug GmbH, which was formed in 1986. The project is managed by the NATO Eurofighter and Tornado Management Agency, which also acts as the prime customer.[NEWLINE]Development of the aircraft effectively began in 1983 with the Future European Fighter Aircraft programme, a multinational collaborative effort between the UK, Germany, France, Italy and Spain. Because of disagreements over design authority and operational requirements, France left the consortium to develop the Dassault Rafale independently instead. A technology demonstration aircraft, the British Aerospace EAP, first took flight on 6 August 1986; the first prototype of the finalised Eurofighter made its first flight on 27 March 1994. The name of the aircraft, Typhoon, was formally adopted in September 1998; the first production contracts were signed that same year.[NEWLINE]Political issues in the partner nations significantly protracted the Typhoon's development; the sudden end of the Cold War reduced European demand for fighter aircraft, and there was debate over the cost and work share of the Eurofighter. The Typhoon was introduced into operational service in 2003. Currently, the type has entered service with the Austrian Air Force, the Italian Air Force, the German Air Force, the Royal Air Force, the Spanish Air Force, and the Royal Saudi Air Force. The Royal Air Force of Oman has also been confirmed as an export customer, bringing the procurement total to 571 aircraft as of 2013.[NEWLINE]The Eurofighter Typhoon is a highly agile aircraft, designed to be an effective dogfighter when in combat with other aircraft; later production aircraft have been increasingly better equipped to undertake air-to-surface strike missions and to be compatible with a likewise increasing number of different armaments and equipment. The Typhoon saw its combat debut during the 2011 military intervention in Libya with the Royal Air Force and the Italian Air Force, performing reconnaissance and ground strike missions. The type has also taken primary responsibility for air-defence duties for the majority of customer nations.[NEWLINE]Credit - Wikipedia
			</Text>
		</Row>
			<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AH64">
				<Text>AH-64 Apache</Text>
			</Row>
			<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_AH64">
				<Text>AH-64 Apache, a modern attack helicopter employed by various armies and air forces.  It uses machine guns, rockets and missles to eliminate enemy threats.
				</Text>
			</Row>
			<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AH64_STRATEGY">
				<Text>The Boeing (formerly McDonnell Douglas, formerly Hughes) AH-64A Apache is the Army's primary attack helicopter. It is a quick-reacting, airborne weapon system that can fight close and deep to destroy, disrupt, or delay enemy forces. The Apache has been designed to fight and survive during the day, night, and in adverse weather throughout the world. The principal intended mission of the Apache is the destruction of high-value targets with the HELLFIRE missile, primarily hostile armor.
				</Text>
			</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_AH64_TEXT">
			<Text>The Boeing AH-64 Apache is a four-blade, twin-engine attack helicopter with a tailwheel-type landing gear arrangement, and a tandem cockpit for a two-man crew. It features a nose-mounted sensor suite for target acquisition and night vision systems. It is armed with a 30 mm (1.18 in) M230 Chain Gun carried between the main landing gear, under the aircraft's forward fuselage. It has four hardpoints mounted on stub-wing pylons, typically carrying a mixture of AGM-114 Hellfire missiles and Hydra 70 rocket pods. The AH-64 has a large amount of systems redundancy to improve combat survivability.[NEWLINE]The Apache originally started as the Model 77 developed by Hughes Helicopters for the United States Army's Advanced Attack Helicopter program to replace the AH-1 Cobra. The prototype YAH-64 was first flown on 30 September 1975. The U.S. Army selected the YAH-64 over the Bell YAH-63 in 1976, and later approved full production in 1982. After purchasing Hughes Helicopters in 1984, McDonnell Douglas continued AH-64 production and development. The helicopter was introduced to U.S. Army service in April 1986. The first production AH-64D Apache Longbow, an upgraded Apache variant, was delivered to the Army in March 1997. Production has been continued by Boeing Defense, Space and Security; over 2,000 AH-64s have been produced to date.[NEWLINE]The U.S. Army is the primary operator of the AH-64; it has also become the primary attack helicopter of multiple nations, including Greece, Japan, Israel, the Netherlands and Singapore; as well as being produced under license in the United Kingdom as the AgustaWestland Apache. U.S. AH-64s have served in conflicts in Panama, the Persian Gulf, Kosovo, Afghanistan, and Iraq. Israel used the Apache in its military conflicts in Lebanon and the Gaza Strip; British and Dutch Apaches have seen deployments in Afghanistan and Iraq.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>